paymentasia.com 2019-07-16

# Privacy Policy | PaymentAsia

### Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to Payment Asia (“Payment Asia”) and we will keep your personal information confidential. This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) applies to the use of Payment Asia’s website (the “Site”).

#### Personal Information Collected

We collect some personal data from you in various ways when you use the Site. The provision of your personal information to us is optional, but without it we may not be able to let you use some of the services.

In addition, when you visit the Site, some information may be automatically collected. For example, it is standard for your Web browser to automatically send information to every Website you visit including ours. That information includes your computer`s Internet Protocol (IP) address, access times, browser type and language, and referring Web site addresses. We may also collect information about your computer`s operating system and information about your usage and activity on the Site. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the Site, to track users` movements around the Site and to gather demographic information about our user-base as a whole.

#### Cookies

We may automatically collect certain information through the use of “cookies.” Cookies are small data files that track and collect your browsing information from your web browser. Among other things, the use of cookies helps us to improve the Site and your experience. We use cookies to see which areas and features are most popular, to count the number of computers accessing our Sites, to personalize your experience, and to remember your preferences. Cookies will also use that information during your future visits to the Site, so that the server may immediately recognize that you have been to the website before.

We link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on the Site. If your browser is set not to accept cookies or if you reject a cookie, you may not be able to access certain features or services of the Site. The use of cookies by our service providers is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies.

#### Use of Personal Information We Collect

We use your personal information to provide you with services, to operate and improve the Site , to send you messages, and for other purposes described in this Policy or disclosed to you on our Sites or in connection with our services. For example, we may use the information we collect from you the Site to:

  * to register for an account with us to build an application;
  * to apply to become a partner;
  * to personalize and improve your experience on the Site;
  * to respond to comments and questions and provide customer service;
  * to deliver service messages and other services and content you request and to send information related to accounts and services, including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;
  * to send you information about new promotions, products, and services offered by Payment Asia and our selected partners; and
  * to conduct an aggregated analysis of the performance of promotions.

Payment Asia may store and process personal information in their own database only.

#### Sharing of Personal Information

We use third parties such as a credit card processing company to bill you for services, an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf, a company to provide our forums and an employment resources company to process your job applications. When you sign up for our services, we will share the personal information you provide only as necessary for the third party to provide that service.

Payment Asia will co-own data that may include your name and email address. If we co-own your personal data all campaign entry forms will have a Payment Asia mailing list Opt-In. We may use aggregate data collected for internal analysis purposes.

We do not share your personal information with third parties other than as described above and as follows:

  * with third party vendors, consultants and other service providers (“Service Providers”) who are working on our behalf and need access to your information to carry out their work for us;

to

  1. comply with laws or respond to lawful requests and legal process,
  2. to protect the rights and property of Payment Asia, our agents, members, and others including to enforce our agreements, policies and terms of use, or
  3. in the good faith belief that disclosure is needed to respond to an emergency or protect the personal safety of any person; and

in connection with any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company. In any such event, we will provide notice if your data is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

 _DIRECT MARKETING_

We intend to use your personal data for direct marketing purposes. We need to obtain your consent (including representation of no objection) before using such data. Please note:

i.          We will not transmit or disclose any of your personal data to any third party for direct marketing purposes without your consent. However, we may transmit and disclose your name, address, telephone number and email address to our group companies in Hong Kong or overseas for direct marketing of their products in relation to payment services;

ii.          We may use data from time to time collected or kept by us, including your name, address, telephone number and electronic mail address, for direct marketing purpose;

iii.         In order to conduct the above direct marketing, we may engage third party data processors or service providers (including, without limitation, milk powder distributors, logistics companies, data companies, telecommunication companies and information technology companies) to complete the tasks.

When you give your consent (including no objection) in relation to the above use to us, you represent that you have consented to our use of your personal data for the above purposes. You will have an option to choose when you provide such information.

Moreover, we may disclose information if requested by authorities, courts or tribunals under applicable laws.

#### Choices About Use of Your Information

You may “opt-out” of receiving promotional emails from Payment Asia by following the instructions in those emails. You may also send requests relating to promotional messages by emailing [services@paymentasia.com](mailto:services@paymentasia.com).  Opt-out requests will not apply to transactional service messages, including messages about your current Payment Asia account and services. If you do not wish us to use your personal data at any time and/or have any enquiries as to how we use your personal data, you may contact us at the email address above.

 _SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION_

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

Payment Asia takes reasonable security measures to protect your personal information to prevent loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Please be aware, however, that despite our efforts, no security measures are impenetrable.

If you use a password on our Site, you are responsible for keeping it confidential. Do not share it with any other person. If you believe your password has been misused, please advise us immediately.

#### Updating and Accessing Your Personal Information

If your personal information changes, we invite you to correct or update your information as soon as possible. You can request changes or access to your information by emailing [services@paymentasia.com](mailto:services@paymentasia.com) .

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account, request that we no longer use your information to provide you services or delete your personal information, contact us at [services@paymentasia.com](mailto:services@paymentasia.com) . We will respond to your request to have your personal information deleted within 30 days. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

 _Keeping your personal information_

We will keep all personal data confidential. Personal information shall only be retained by us for the period of time which is necessary to fulfill the purpose of use of such data (including any purpose directly related).

#### Links To Other Sites

The Site may link to other Websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Payment Asia. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

#### Testimonials

We may post customer testimonials on the Site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer`s consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you wish to request that your testimonial be removed you may do so by emailing us at [services@paymentasia.com](mailto:services@paymentasia.com).

#### Social Media Features

The Site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

#### Changes To This Policy

Payment Asia may change this Policy from time to time. If we make any changes to this Policy, we will change the “Last Updated” date above. If there are material changes to this policy, we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account). We encourage you to review this Policy whenever you visit our Sites or use our Applications to understand how your personal information is used.

#### Questions About This Policy

If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us at [services@paymentasia.com](mailto:services@paymentasia.com).
